http://www.djsports.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
- D&J Sports
JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.
You must have JavaScript enabled in your browser to utilize the functionality of this website.
Call 1-800-460-7946
Retail Store Locations
Contact Us
Help
Get FREE Shipping when you spend $49+, some restrictions apply see details
Low Price Guarantee! Check Now
COVID-19 UPDATE: Please call your local store for temporary hour changes or closures.
D&J Sports Swim Shop
Search:
Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Compare
You have no items to compare.
Menu
Women Technical Racing SwimsuitsCompetition SwimwearAquatic Fitness SwimwearWomen's Swim CapsWomen's Swim GogglesTwo PiecesLifeguard SuitsWater Polo SuitsPractice SwimwearWomen's FootwearWomens ApparelMen Men's Technical Racing SwimsuitsJammer SwimsuitsSwim BriefsDrag SuitsSquare Leg SuitsMen's Lifeguard SuitsWater Shorts & BoardshortsMen's Water Polo SuitsPractice SwimsuitsMens ApparelBrands AccusplitAGONAnti-WaveAquaSphereArenaColorado TimeCompetitorD&J SportsDolfinFinisHydroISTMack'sMalibu CMikasaMichael PhelpsNikeOceanRDPRYKASeafollySeikoSpeedoSportCountStretchCordzStrokeMakersSummer SolutionsSwim StuffSwimSprayTake Your MarkTKOTriggerpointTYRUltrakZealiosKids Girls SwimwearBoys SwimwearKids Swim AccessoriesKids ApparelSwim Gear Swim Goggles Speedo VanquisherFitness GogglesPrescription Swim GogglesKids GogglesPerformance GogglesNike Performance Swim Caps Silicone Swim CapsLatex Swim CapsLycra Swim CapsPull BuoysSwim FinsSwim KickboardsSwim PaddlesSwim SnorkelsMesh Swim Gear BagsSwim Towels & ChamoisSwim Training AidsMedicine BallsSwim Stretch CordsRollers & MassagersSwim Backpacks & Duffle Bags Swimming BackpacksSwim Mesh BagCoaches Briefcases Arena Carbon Pro Gift CardsPersonal Care Swim Shampoo & ConditionerEar & Nose PlugsSwimsuit CleanersMP3, Electronics, & Timing Wrist WatchesSwim Stop WatchesSwim MP3 PlayersWater Aerobics BarbellsJog BeltsAqua GlovesFitness Swim KickboardsWater Aerobic ShoesWater Polo BallsSwim Awards & Ribbons Swim RibbonsSwimming StuffDC Superhero CollectionSwim Training Gear PackageApparel Swim ParkasSwim Warm-UpsSwim T-ShirtsSwim HoodiesSwim ShortsHats & VisorsSwim Polo ShirtsLifeguard Lifeguard Swimwear Ladies Lifeguard SuitsMens Guard ShortsLifeguard ApparelLifeguard Equipment/Rescue Equipment Rescue TubesGuard SpineboardsRing BuoysRescue MasksFirst Aid KitsPool Rescue EquipmentRescue CansLifeguard AccessoriesLifeguard ChairsPool Equipment Lane Lines, Parts, Storage Reels Lane LinesStorage ReelsReplacement PartsBackstroke FlagsPool StorageSwim Pace Clocks & Lap CountersStarting & Timing EquipmentStarting BlocksWater Polo Goals
TEAM SALES
The Dedicated Swimmer's Outfitter
We are here to service you and your team. Everything you need from real swimmers, with stores near you.
Get Started Today
About D&J Sports
CUSTOM SWIM TEAM SERVICES
We have a full service in-house team of experts from artwork to screen printing and embroidery, that will create the look you want for your swim team.
Custom Swim Caps
Custom Swim Team Suits
Custom Team T-shirts
Custom Team Towels
Custom Swim Team Banners
Custom Swim Team Car Decals
Custom Mesh Bags
Custom Embroidery & Tackle Twill
Custom Water Bottles
Custom Swim Team Apparel Catalog
TEAM DEPARTMENT
We are a full service swim team dealer with swimsuits and swim gear from all of the brands you want.
New Swim Team & Discounts
Swim Team Suit Package Deals
Swim Meet Event T-shirts
Swim Suit Fittings & Swim Meet/Event Sales
Team Sponsorship Programs
Summer League Suits
5k Race T-shirt Printing
CUSTOM TEAM STORE
Easy team ordering with our individual custom swim team stores. Your swimmers and parents can order individually and get the team prices and orders shipped directly to their door step.
Easy Team Ordering
Team Login
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Email:
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.
When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.
Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To quickly process your transactions.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. Ifyou have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.
How do we protect visitor information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.
Do we use "cookies"?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include D&J Sports. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).
Changes to our policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on March 11, 2010.
Questions and feedback
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.
Online Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Customer Service
Contact Us
About Us
Store Locations
Gift Cards
Size Chart
Store Policies
Privacy Policy
Pool Storage
© 2019 D&J Sports Inc. All Rights Reserved. The best selection of custom swim team suits, fitness swimwear, water aerobics swimwear, elite racing swimsuits, lifeguard suits, swim team parkas, and custom printed t-shirts.
